{
  "next_card_id": 9,
  "next_skill_id": 1,
  "epsilon": 0.2,
  "cards": [
    {
      "card_id": 1,
      "front": "Front",
      "back": "Back",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.6235294117647058,
      "attempts": 1,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T13:47:58.446471",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T13:47:58.446471",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 2,
      "front": "Hola",
      "back": "Hello",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.6235294117647058,
      "attempts": 1,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T13:48:03.636952",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T13:48:03.636952",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 1,
      "front": "b",
      "back": "2",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.7017563759047051,
      "attempts": 3,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T13:48:17.622340",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T13:48:17.622340",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 2,
      "front": "2",
      "back": "3",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.6235294117647058,
      "attempts": 1,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T16:36:41.034745",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T16:36:41.034745",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 3,
      "front": "3",
      "back": "3",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.6235294117647058,
      "attempts": 1,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T16:36:43.026917",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T16:36:43.026917",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 4,
      "front": "3",
      "back": "3",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.6235294117647058,
      "attempts": 1,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T16:36:44.625888",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T16:36:44.625888",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 5,
      "front": "3",
      "back": "3",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.7017563759047051,
      "attempts": 3,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T16:36:55.946498",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T16:36:55.946498",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 6,
      "front": "3",
      "back": "3",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.7398928810960008,
      "attempts": 4,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T16:36:57.354838",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T16:36:57.354838",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 7,
      "front": "3",
      "back": "3",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.6235294117647058,
      "attempts": 1,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T16:36:50.753323",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T16:36:50.753323",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    },
    {
      "card_id": 8,
      "front": "1",
      "back": "2",
      "skill_ids": [
        1
      ],
      "p_known": 0.7398928810960008,
      "attempts": 4,
      "correct": 1,
      "last_review": "2025-11-22T16:37:35.218411",
      "next_due": "2025-11-23T16:37:35.218411",
      "interval_days": 1.0
    }
  ],
  "skills": [
    {
      "skill_id": 1,
      "name": "Demonstration Deck",
      "p_learn": 0.09294812541918003,
      "p_slip": 0.1,
      "p_guess": 0.2
    }
  ]
}